searchforancestors.com 2013-06-16

# Privacy Statement at Ancestor Search

####  Privacy Statement for Ancestor Search 

**Ancestor Search** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Ancestor Search ](http://www.searchforancestors.com/)

##  This Web site does not have pop-ups 

This Web site does not have pop-up advertisements. If you are receiving pop-up ads when you visit this site, the ads are probably coming from spyware that was downloaded and installed on your computer without your permission from another site. To delete this unwanted spyware from your computer, download the FREE spyware remover from Microsoft. [Microsoft Anti-Spyware](http://www.microsoft.com/athome/security/spyware/software/default.mspx)

##  Personal Information 

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

##  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. 

##  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Ancestor Search** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

##  Special Relationships 

Some of the advertisements may contain cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs, deliver viruses to your computer, or deliver e-mail spam. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies received with banner ads may be collected by the ad company to record the number of times an advertisement was shown. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   
|    

|  Free at Ancestry.com   
---  

       **It's Easy to Get Started!**
*   [**Build your family tree**](http://www.searchforancestors.com/link.php?m=buildatree) online for FREE! Ancestry.com will use what you enter to find more about your family's ancestors. 
The largest collection of historic records and family trees. 
All Access Ancestry.com 14 day free trial. You'll be amazed what you can find! 
Free Ancestry.com databases listed by location and popularity.   
  
Site Features   
---  

Search for your ancestors by record type. 
Search for your ancestors by country. 
Free genealogy resources: charts, lessons, software, databases, look ups, relationship charts, form letters, translation services. 
Free trial to Ancestry.com. Why pay when you can view for free? 
Special offers, coupons, coupon codes, discounts, sales & deals 
Family Tree Maker 2012 list of improvements   
  
Search Help   
---  

Find your family in the online databases of digitized original world-wide records. 
Learn the unique features of each Social Security Death Index and specific search techniques to use for each. 
Search the oldest free genealogy website of transcriptions. 
Find people in the US white pages and reverse directory. 
Step by step guide to help find long lost relatives.
